## JONAH DLIN

# FULL STACK DEVELOPER

jonahdlin.com

**4**16 274 1784

in jonah-dlin-00b281106/

n ionahdlin

### **EDUCATION**

University of Waterloo

BMath Computational Mathematics 2020

## **SKILLS**

#### **TOOLS**

Bash

Git

Excel

AWS

Lambda

S3

DynamoDB

CloudWatch

SOS

CloudFormation

## LANGUAGES & FRAMEWORKS

React/Redux

JavaScript

HTML5/CSS3

TypeScript

Flow

Python

Node.js

#### **HOBBIES**

Music

Drums

Piano

Guitar

Bass guitar

**PC** Gaming

Web-based Side Projects

Sheet Music Editor

**Graph Visualizer** 

**Evolution Simulator** 

## **SUMMARY**

I am a flexible and capable full stack developer specializing in TypeScript, React and Redux frontends, as well as Python and Node.js backends for both premise and cloud-based applications. I thrive in work environments ranging from independent projects to sprawling international collaborations. I write solid, clean code and projects I completed for Genesys and Wish are now used by millions of people.

### **EMPLOYMENT**

**Genesys** 

Markham, ON

Full Stack Developer

Sept. 2019 to Dec. 2019

- Developed calendar sharing infrastructure using AWS Lambda, S3, DynamoDB and CloudWatch
- Optimized existing AWS code by developing performance analysis scripts in Python
- Independently owned and investigated project architecture and best practices

Wish

San Francisco, CA

Full Stack Web Developer

Jan. 2019 to Apr. 2019

- Boosted central feature's load speed and scalability by overhauling Backbone.js pages in React/Redux
- Wrote and enhanced web APIs in Python while ensuring flexibility and reusability
- Initiated new project management paradigm which was successfully adopted by the team

Genesys

Markham, ON

Frontend Web Application Developer

May 2018 to Aug. 2018

- Completed key features of workforce management application in React, Redux and TypeScript
- Excelled in large, worldwide team of developers using Gitlab, JIRA, and Kanban process
- Honed technical presentation skills by demoing at weekly standups
- Wrote developer's guide to the project codebase and used it to onboard new developers

#### **University of Toronto**

Toronto, ON

Frontend Web Developer

Sept. 2017 to Dec. 2017

- Created interactive biological net search and viewer using React, Cytoscape.js and JS
- Developed collaborative editing capabilities using Node.js, Socket.io and RethinkDB

## **Humber Institute of Technology**

Etobicoke, ON

Math Tutor

Jan. 2017 to Apr. 2017

- Quickly learned concepts in statistics, programming and finance to teach to college students
- Organized promotional class visits by communicating with professors and coordinating schedules
- Reduced amount of missed class visits by writing a scheduling app to alert staff

### **ACCOMPLISHMENTS**

#### **Dean's Honours List**

University of Waterloo

University of Waterloo distinction for graduating with over 87% average

#### **Outstanding Work Record**

University of Waterloo

Received outstanding work evaluations from internship employers for taking initiative, learning quickly, and adapting to new environments